F/S MONOGRAM

Agustin Gutierrez

OBJECTIVE

I am a student at IUPUI (Indiana University Purdue University Indianapolis) working towards my Bachelors of Science (in MAS Web Design & Development). In both my academic and professional life, I have been consistently praised as hard-working by my professors and peers while excelling in a multitude of roles. Whether working on academic, extracurricular, or job responsibilities. I apply proven teamwork, multitasking and communication skills, which I hope to present in this position!



ADDRESS Indianapolis, IN 46214 USA



PHONE 317-292-3116



EMAIL

aggutie@iu.edı



GitHub/Portfolio Site

https://github.com/agggutiehttps://a gggutie.github.io/Web-Development-Portfolio/

EXPERIENCE

03/2022 - Current Position

Allied Security Officer • Allied Universal • Indianapolis, IN

• Audit and record all documentation to Microsoft Office applications (Word and Excel).

12/2020 - 03/2021

Phlebotomist • Collection Sites LLC. • Greenwood, IN

- Facilitated Covid testing by nasal swab or finger pricking for appointments or walk-ins
- Entered patients' insurance information into a computer-based system for proper lab delivery and verification

08/2020 - 12/2020

Intern • IU (Indiana University) Studios • Indianapolis, IN

- Collaborated with studio team to train in various areas of the studio such as Photography, User Experience, and Marketing
- Training tracking/interpreting social media analytics

05/2019 - 11/2020

Ambassador/Call Center • IU North Hospital • Carmel, IN

• Managed calls from patients ordering food by viewing their dietary restrictions in Cerner to ensure their orders aligned with their diet restrictions.

EDUCATION

08/2019 - Currently attending

IUPUI • Indianapolis IN

 Bachelors of Science in Media Arts & Science with a specialization in Web Design & Development.

08/2016 - 06/2019

Ben Davis University High School

 $\bullet \qquad \text{Associates of Science in Health Science (through Vincennes University)}.$